usage: png2icons-cli infile outfile format [-nn | - bl | -bc | -bz | -hm] [-i]

Don't append a file extension to outfile, it will be set automatically.

format    (output format):
  -icns   Apple ICNS format, creates <outfile>.icns
  -ico    Windows ICO format, creates <outfile>.ico (contained icons as BMP)
  -icop   Windows ICO format, creates <outfile>.ico (contained icons as PNG)
  -icowe  Windows ICO format, creates <outfile>.ico  (for Windows executables)
  -all    Create both ICNS and ICO format (ICO with BMP)
  -allp   Create both ICNS and ICO format (ICO with PNG)
  -allwe  Create both ICNS and ICO format (ICO for Windows executables)

Scaling algorithms:
  -nn (Nearest Neighbor)
  -bl (Bilinear)
  -bc (Bicubic, default)
  -bz (Bezier)
  -hm (Hermite)
  -bc2 (Bicubic, alternative faster version)

-i  print messages
